Finding Aid for the Chancellor's Office Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Radnor Lake Preservation Association, Inc. 1975-77 (Box 0212, Folder 20)
- Radnor Lake 1972 (Box 0212, Folder 21)
- Ralston Purina 1969 (Box 0212, Folder 22)
- Rand Hall 1963-69 (Box 0212, Folder 23)
- Rand Hall 1957-62 (Box 0212, Folder 24)
- Rand Dining Hall--Francis W. Warfield, Architect 1949-52 (Box 0212, Folder 25)
- Rand Hall 1948-56 (Box 0212, Folder 26)
- Rand Room 1973 (Box 0212, Folder 27)
- Rasmussen, E. G. 1943-56 (Box 0212, Folder 28)
- Ra-Rd Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0213, Folder 1)
- Ra-Rd Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0213, Folder 2)
- Regan, Donald September 15, 1970 (Box 0213, Folder 3)
- Regional Conference on Humanities and Public Policy 5/27/76 (Box 0213, Folder 4)
- Reiss, Albert J., Jr. 1952-55 (Box 0213, Folder 5)
- Reiss, Albert J., Jr. 1955-58 (Box 0213, Folder 6)
- Religion, Department of 1955-57 (Box 0213, Folder 7)
- Religious Heritage of America September 12, 1967--May 1969 (Box 0213, Folder 8)
- Rental Properties 1951 (Box 0213, Folder 9)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1976-77: Requisitions 3020-638 Entertainment 1976-77 (Box 0213, Folder 10)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1976-77: Requisitions 3020-683 Other Expenses 1976-77 (Box 0213, Folder 11)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1976-77: Requisitions 3020-718 Telephone, long distance 1976-77 (Box 0213, Folder 12)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 3020-719 1976-77: Requisitions 3020-719 Travel 1976-77 (Box 0213, Folder 13)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1976-77: Requisitions 3020-819 Auto Replacement 1976-77 (Box 0213, Folder 14)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1976-77: Requisitions 0000-3251 1976-77 (Box 0213, Folder 15)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1976-77 (Box 0213, Folder 16)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1975-76: Requisitions 3020-638 Entertainment 1975-76 (Box 0213, Folder 17)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1975-76: Requisitions 3020-683 Other Expenses 1975-76 (Box 0213, Folder 18)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1975-76: Requisitions 3020-691 Office Supplies 1975-76 (Box 0213, Folder 19)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1975-76: Requisitions 3020-719 Travel 1975-76 (Box 0213, Folder 20)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1975-76 (Box 0213, Folder 21)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1974-75: Requisitions, etc. 3020-638 Entertainment 1974-75 (Box 0213, Folder 22)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1974-75: Requisitions, etc. 3020-683 Other Expenses 1974-75 (Box 0213, Folder 23)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1974-75: Requisitions, etc. 3020-718 Telephone, Lg. D. and Telegraph (Box 0213, Folder 24)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1974-75: Requisitions, etc. 0000-3020-719-40 Travel 1974-75 (Box 0213, Folder 25)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1974-75 (Box 0213, Folder 26)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1973-74: Requisitions, etc. 3020-638 Entertainment 1973-74 (Box 0213, Folder 27)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1973-74: Requisitions, etc. 0000-3020-719-40 Travel 1973-74 (Box 0213, Folder 28)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1973-74 (Box 0213, Folder 29)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1972-73: 3020-638 72-73 (Box 0213, Folder 30)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1972-73: 3020-683 Other Expenses 72-73 (Box 0213, Folder 31)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1972-73: Requisitions 0000-3020-719-40 1972-73 (Box 0213, Folder 32)
- Requisitions and Other Charge Forms 1972-73 (Box 0213, Folder 33)
- Requisitions 1971-72: 1300-3020-082-40 Dan forth Short-Term Leave Grant to Alexander Heard (Box 0213, Folder 34)
- Requisitions 1971-72: 0000-3020-638-40 (entertainment) 1971-72 (Box 0213, Folder 35)
- Requisitions 1971-72 (Box 0213, Folder 36)
- Requisitions and Other Budget Charges 1970-71: 0000-3020-714-40 White House Assignment (Box 0213, Folder 37)
- Requisitions and Other Budget Charges 1970-71: 0000-3020-638-40 Entertainment 1970-71 (Box 0213, Folder 38)
- Requisitions and Other Budget Charges 1970-71: 0000-3020-719-40 Travel (Box 0213, Folder 39)
- Requisitions and Other Budget Charges 1970-71 (Box 0213, Folder 40)
- Requisitions and Work Orders--Fiscal Year 1969-70: Budget 01-0101-858 Travel (Box 0213, Folder 41)
- Requisitions and Other Work Orders--Fiscal Year 1969-70: Budget 01-0101-860 Entertainment 1969-70 (Box 0213, Folder 42)
- Requisitions and Work Orders--Fiscal Year 1969-70 (Box 0213, Folder 43)
- Requisitions 1969 (Box 0213, Folder 44)
- Requisitions 1967-68 (Box 0213, Folder 45)
- Republican Party Matters 1967-69 (Box 0213, Folder 46)
- Research Council, University, Dean of the Graduate School, Chair 1964-65 (Box 0213, Folder 47)
- Research Corporation July 29, 1970 (Box 0213, Folder 48)
- Research Corporation--Frederick Gardner Cottrell Special Grant 1946-67 (Box 0213, Folder 49)
- Research Grants 1957 (Box 0213, Folder 50)
- Research Park (Willard Brown/Dan Shilstat) 1968-69 (Box 0213, Folder 51)
- Research Program--Physics and Astronomy 1950 (Box 0213, Folder 52)
- Research Reactor Conference 1954-57 (Box 0213, Folder 53)
- Resources for the Future, Inc. 1970-74 (Box 0213, Folder 54)
- Resources for the Future, Inc. 1967-69 (Box 0213, Folder 55)
- Retirement Policy 1963-69 (Box 0213, Folder 56)
- Retirement Policy 1947-62 (Box 0213, Folder 57)
- Retirement Policy 1942-46 (Box 0213, Folder 58)
- Reynolds, Mr. and Mrs. W. Glasgow (Nancy DuPont) 1970-74 (Box 0213, Folder 59)
- Reynolds, Mr. and Mrs. W. Glasgow (Nancy DuPont) 1966-69 (Box 0213, Folder 60)
- Reynolds Tobacco Company, R. J. 1970 (Box 0214, Folder 1)
- Rhodes, Peyton N. 1953-55 (Box 0214, Folder 2)
- Rhodes Fellowship Fund, Thomas W. 1953-55 (Box 0214, Folder 3)
- Rhodes Scholarship Committee 1963-69 (Box 0214, Folder 4)
- Rhodes Scholarship Committee 1955-62 (Box 0214, Folder 5)
- Re-Rh Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0214, Folder 6)
- Re-Rh Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0214, Folder 7)
- Rice, Grantland 1970-74 (Box 0214, Folder 8)
- Rice, Grantland 1955-69 (Box 0214, Folder 9)
- Richmond, University of January 27, 1972 (Box 0214, Folder 10)
- Rippel Foundation, Fannie E. May 26, 1971-73 (Box 0214, Folder 11)
- Ri-Rn Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0214, Folder 12)
- Ri-Rn Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0214, Folder 13)
- Roberts, Erb (Superintendant, Plant Operations) 1959-69 (Box 0214, Folder 14)
- Robinson Fund, Stephen T. 1958 (Box 0214, Folder 15)
- Rochedieu, Charles A. 1928-49 (Box 0214, Folder 16)
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund 1975-76 (Box 0214, Folder 17)
- Rockefeller Brothers Theological Fellowship Program-American Association of Theological Schools Fund (Box 0214, Folder 18)
- Rockefeller Foundation (Rockefeller Brothers Fund) 1974 (Box 0214, Folder 19)
- Rockefeller Foundation 1970-73 (Box 0214, Folder 20)
- Rockefeller Foundation 1965-69: Grants for financially disadvantaged high school grads (Atlanta Conference 6/67) (Box 0214, Folder 21)
- Rockefeller Foundation 1965-69 (Box 0214, Folder 22)
- Rockefeller Foundation--Student Assistance Program 1963-64: Visit of Leland DeVinney, Oct. 13, 1965 (Box 0214, Folder 23)
- Rockefeller Foundation--Student Assistance Program 1963-64: Rockefeller Foundation (continued) 1963 (Box 0214, Folder 24)
- Rockefeller Foundation--Student Assistance Program 1963-64 (Box 0214, Folder 25)
- Rockefeller Foundation 1954 (Box 0214, Folder 26)
- Rockefeller Foundation 1951-53 (Box 0214, Folder 27)
- Rockefeller Foundation 1947-50 (Box 0214, Folder 28)
- Rockefeller Foundation (Box 0214, Folder 29)
- Roa-Rof Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0214, Folder 30)
- Roa-Rof Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0214, Folder 31)
- Rogers, David 1967-73 (Box 0215, Folder 1)
- Rogers, David E. 10/65-69 (Box 0215, Folder 2)
- Rogers, David E. 1959-65 (Box 0215, Folder 3)
- Rogosin, Israel 1967-72 (Box 0215, Folder 4)
- Roos, Charles 1970-73 (Box 0215, Folder 5)
- Rotary Club 1972 (Box 0215, Folder 6)
- Rotary Club 1970-71 (Box 0215, Folder 7)
- Rotary Club II 1963-69 (Box 0215, Folder 8)
- Rotary Club 1953-63 (Box 0215, Folder 9)
- Rotary Club--Foundation Fellowships 1966-67 (Box 0215, Folder 10)
- Round Table (Box 0215, Folder 11)
- Rowe, Robert S. (Personal) 1959-62 (Box 0215, Folder 12)
- Rowland Foundation (see Polaroid-Land Foundation) 1974 (Box 0215, Folder 13)
- Rog-Rt Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0215, Folder 14)
- Rog-Rt Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0215, Folder 15)
- Rudnick, Philip 1942-48 (Box 0215, Folder 16)
- Rysan, Josef 1963-69 (Box 0215, Folder 17)
- Rysan, Josef 1955-62 (Box 0215, Folder 18)
- Ru-Rz Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0215, Folder 19)
- Ru-Rz Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0215, Folder 20)
- Sabbatical Leaves 1947-51 (Box 0215, Folder 21)
- Safety, Campus 1970-71 (Box 0215, Folder 22)
- Safety, Campus 1963-69 (Box 0215, Folder 23)
- Safety, Campus 1959-62 (Box 0215, Folder 24)
- Saint Augustine's College, Raleigh, North Carolina 1973-75 (Box 0215, Folder 25)
- St. Catherine's, Oxford (also see Mrs. Rudolph A. Light) 1970-71 (Box 0215, Folder 26)
- Saint Thomas Hospital April 20, 1972-74 (Box 0215, Folder 27)
- Salaries 1967-68 (Box 0216, Folder 1)
- Salaries 1957-66 (Box 0216, Folder 2)
- Salaries 1938-55 (Box 0216, Folder 3)
- Salmon, Christopher 1949-51 (Box 0216, Folder 4)
- Samuels, Seymour, Jr. August 28, 1969-74 (Box 0216, Folder 5)
- Sanborn, Herbert C. 1958-64 (Box 0216, Folder 6)
- Sanborn, Herbert C. 1937-57 (Box 0216, Folder 7)
- Sandmel, Samuel 1960-63 (Box 0216, Folder 8)
- Sandmel, Samuel 1947-58 (Box 0216, Folder 9)
- Sandt, John J. 1948-57 (Box 0216, Folder 10)
- Sanford, Terry 1975 (Box 0216, Folder 11)
- Sanford, Terry January 6, 1970-74 (Box 0216, Folder 12)
- Sanger, William T. (see transfer files) 1957-62 (Box 0216, Folder 13)
- Sanger, William T. 1952-57 (Box 0216, Folder 14)
- Sanger, William T. 1954-55 (Box 0216, Folder 15)
- Saponaro, James N. 1952 (Box 0216, Folder 16)
- Sarratt, Madison 1978 (Box 0216, Folder 17)
- Sarratt, Madison 1975-77 (Box 0216, Folder 18)
- Sarratt, Madison 1970-74 (Box 0216, Folder 19)
- Sarratt, Madison 1966-69 (Box 0216, Folder 20)
- Sarratt, Madison 1956-65 (Box 0216, Folder 21)
- Sarratt, C. Madison 1933-55 (Box 0216, Folder 22)
- Sarratt Student Center 1970-73 (Box 0216, Folder 23)
- Sarratt Student Center 1967-69 (Box 0216, Folder 24)
- Sarratt Prize, Madison 1965-69 (Box 0216, Folder 25)
- Satterfield, M. H. 1948-49 (Box 0216, Folder 26)
- Savannah Country Day School (Thomas F. Triol Headmaster) April 9, 1971 (Box 0216, Folder 27)
- Sa-Sb Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0216, Folder 28)
- Sa-Sb Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0216, Folder 29)
- Sa-Si Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0217, Folder 1)
- Scarritt College 1970-74 (Box 0217, Folder 2)
- Scarritt College 1963-69 (Box 0217, Folder 3)
- Scarritt College 1957-62 (Box 0217, Folder 4)
- Schenley Industries Fund for Improvement of Faculty Salaries Established 1959 in Honor of Lewis S. Rosenstiel (Box 0217, Folder 5)
- Scholarships, Miscellaneous 1963-69 (Box 0217, Folder 6)
- Scholarships (Miscellaneous) 1957-62 (Box 0217, Folder 7)
- Scholarship, Waite P. Fishel 1954-56 (Box 0217, Folder 8)
- Scholarship Fund, William P. Campbell 1949-50 (Box 0217, Folder 9)
- Scholarship, Phil Connell (and d. Mrs. Witter correspondence) 1940-65 (Box 0217, Folder 10)
- Scholarship Fund, Maggie S. Craig 1942-67 (Box 0217, Folder 11)
- Scholarship, Elliston 1909-58 (Box 0217, Folder 12)
- Scholarships, National Merit 1954-58 (Box 0217, Folder 13)
- Scholarship Fund, Newton H. White 1955-58 (Box 0217, Folder 14)
- Scholarship Fund, I. B. Tigrett Memorial 1954-56 (Box 0217, Folder 15)
- Scholarship Fund, Owsley Manier 1955 (Box 0217, Folder 16)
- Scholarship Foundation, Japanese 1951 (Box 0217, Folder 17)
- Scholarship, John Milford Williams (Galloway Women's College) 1950 (Box 0217, Folder 18)
- Scholarship, William Northern 1944-50 (Box 0217, Folder 19)
- Scholarship, J. C. Foshee 1939-50 (Box 0217, Folder 20)
- Scholarship, Leopold and Pauline Kaufman--E. R. Kaufman 1937-47 (Box 0217, Folder 21)
- Scholarships, Emergency 1944-45 (Box 0217, Folder 22)
- Scholarship, Sarah Overton Colton Barry Memorial 1939 (Box 0217, Folder 23)
- Scholarship--under will of Arthur Williams, through Chemical Bank and Trust Company 1946-47 (Box 0217, Folder 24)
- Scholarship Prize, Walter G. Kirkpatrick 1919-25 (Box 0217, Folder 25)
- Sca-Sch Miscllaneou Correspondence (Box 0217, Folder 26)
- Scott, Jr., William H.--Department of Surgery 1966- (Box 0217, Folder 27)
- Sci-Sd Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0217, Folder 28)
- Sci-Sd Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0217, Folder 29)
- Seal of the University 1963-69 (Box 0217, Folder 30)
- Seal of the University 1946-62 (Box 0217, Folder 31)
- Seal of the University 1942-46 (Box 0217, Folder 32)
- Sealantic Fund 1963-69 (Box 0217, Folder 33)
- Seatlantic Fund, The 1952-62 (Box 0217, Folder 34)
- Sealtest 1967-71 (Box 0217, Folder 35)
- Selective Service 1968-69 (Box 0217, Folder 36)
- Selective Service System 1940-51 (Box 0217, Folder 37)
- Sellers, Ava F. 1949-62 (Box 0217, Folder 38)
- Semester System (See transfer file) 1955-57 (Box 0217, Folder 39)
- Semester System (Ewing P. Shahan) 1951-57 (Box 0217, Folder 40)
- University Senate (Box 0217, Folder 41)
- University Senate (Box 0217, Folder 42)
- University Senate--Minutes of meetings 1963-66 (Box 0217, Folder 43)
- Se-Sg Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0217, Folder 44)
- Se-Sg Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0217, Folder 45)
- Shahan, Ewing P. 1963-69 (Box 0217, Folder 46)
- Shahan, Ewing P. 7/60-62 (Box 0217, Folder 47)
- Shanks, E. Baylis 1963-69 (Box 0218, Folder 1)
- Sharp, Walter 1948-61 (Box 0218, Folder 2)
- Shea, Edward J. 1956-58 (Box 0218, Folder 3)
- Shell Companies Foundation 77-79 (Box 0218, Folder 4)
- Shell Companies Foundation 1974-76 (Box 0218, Folder 5)
- Shell Companies Foundation 1970- (Box 0218, Folder 6)
- Shell Companies Foundation 1963-69 (Box 0218, Folder 7)
- Shell Companies Foundation 1957-62 (Box 0218, Folder 8)
- Sha-Shh Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0218, Folder 9)
- Sha-Shh Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0218, Folder 10)
- Shore, Dinah 1944-68 (Box 0218, Folder 11)
- C. Sam Shoup 1943-51 (Box 0218, Folder 12)
- Shi-Shz Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0218, Folder 13)
- Shi-Shz Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0218, Folder 14)
- Sigma Xi 1963-69 (Box 0218, Folder 15)
- Sigma Xi 1947-62 (Box 0218, Folder 16)
- Sigma Xi 1944-46 (Box 0218, Folder 17)
- Silberman, Lou H. 1970- (Box 0218, Folder 18)
- Silberman, Lou H. 1963-69 (Box 0218, Folder 19)
- Silberman, Lou H. 1952-62 (Box 0218, Folder 20)
- Simon, Maron J. 1969-74 (Box 0218, Folder 21)
- Simpson, Jr., George L. 1965-69 (Box 0218, Folder 22)
- Simpson, Paul (TV archives) 1968-69 (Box 0218, Folder 23)
- Sims, Wilson (Woody) 1971-73 (Box 0218, Folder 24)
- Skinner Memorial Fund, Eula M. 1955-56 (Box 0218, Folder 25)
- Skull and Bones Club 1942-48 (Box 0218, Folder 26)
- Slack, Francis G. 1977 (Box 0218, Folder 27)
- Slack, Francis G. 1946-51 (Box 0218, Folder 28)
- Sleeth, Ronald E. 1969-72 (Box 0218, Folder 29)
- Sloan Foundation, Alfred P. 1974-76 (Box 0218, Folder 30)
- Sloan Foundation, Alfred P. 1973- (Box 0218, Folder 31)
- Sloan Foundation, Alfred P. 1970- (Box 0218, Folder 32)
- Sloan Foundation, Alfred P. (See transfer file) 12/64-69 (Box 0218, Folder 33)
- Sloan Foundation Conference, Alfred P., Onchiota Conference Center, Sterling Forest, Tuxedo, NY 9/11-13 (Box 0218, Folder 34)
- Sloan Foundation, Inc., Alfred P. thru 10/64 (Box 0218, Folder 35)
- Sloan Foundation, Alfred P. (Harold S. Sloan) 1938-54 (Box 0218, Folder 36)
- Sloan, George A. 1950-55 (Box 0218, Folder 37)
- Sloan, George A. 1936-49 (Box 0218, Folder 38)
- Sloan Professor of Metallurgy, The George A. 1957 (Box 0218, Folder 39)
- Si-Smh Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0218, Folder 40)
- Si-Smh Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0218, Folder 41)
- Smith, Frank C. March 10, 1971-73 (Box 0218, Folder 42)
- Smith, George M. 1953-55 (Box 0218, Folder 43)
- Smith, J. Holt February 4, 1972-73 (Box 0218, Folder 44)
- Smith, Mrs J. H. (Kate Tillett) 1950-64 (Box 0218, Folder 45)
- Smith, James Mapheus June 18, 1969-74 (Box 0218, Folder 46)
- Smith, James 3-1-66 to Present (Box 0218, Folder 47)
- Smith, T. Lynn 1941-49 (Box 0218, Folder 48)
- Smith 1968-74 (Box 0218, Folder 49)
- Smi-Smz Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0218, Folder 50)
- Smi-Smz Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 0218, Folder 51)
- Synder, John W. 1947-52 (Box 0219, Folder 1)
- Social Science Center 1970-74 (Box 0219, Folder 2)
- Social Science Center 1968-69 (Box 0219, Folder 3)
- Social Science Research Council 1949-62 (Box 0219, Folder 4)
- Social Security 1963-69 (Box 0219, Folder 5)
- Social Security 1950-62 (Box 0219, Folder 6)
- Sociology, Department of 1970 (Box 0219, Folder 7)
- Sociology, Department of 1964-69 (Box 0219, Folder 8)
- South Central Bell 1970-74 (Box 0219, Folder 9)
- South, University of 1971-73 (Box 0219, Folder 10)
- Southern Agriculturist Fellowships 1948-49 (Box 0219, Folder 11)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools: Montgomery Bell Proceedings (Box 0219, Folder 12)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools: Schedule, Team Roster and Bio-Data (Box 0219, Folder 13)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools: Correspondence concerning visit (Box 0219, Folder 14)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools: Buffet Supper at DPD 3/16/75, 5:15 pm (Box 0219, Folder 15)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools: Vanderbilt University and Peabody College 3/17/75 11-11:50 (Box 0219, Folder 16)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools: Trustee lunch 3/18/75, 12 noon (Box 0219, Folder 17)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (Box 0219, Folder 18)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS) 1974 (Box 0219, Folder 19)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools Miscellaneous 1972-73 (Box 0219, Folder 20)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools Miscellany 1970-71 (Box 0219, Folder 21)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1966-69 (Box 0219, Folder 22)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (also see Long-Range Planning files) 1965 (Box 0219, Folder 23)
- Southern Association Project--trip file for June 24-25, 1964 meeting, Durham, N.C. (Box 0219, Folder 24)
- Southern Association Project--trip file for Feb. 18, 1964 meeting (Box 0219, Folder 25)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1964-65 (Box 0219, Folder 26)
- Southern Association 1952-63 (Box 0219, Folder 27)
- Southern Association Athletic Committee Report 1954 (Box 0219, Folder 28)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (See transfer file) 1962-64 (Box 0220, Folder 1)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (Constitution) Nov. 1962 (Box 0220, Folder 2)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (Correspondence) 1926-47 (Box 0220, Folder 3)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Education Improvement Project (Reports and Publications) 1967-69 (Box 0220, Folder 4)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Education Improvement Project (Correspondence, agenda, minutes) 1967-69 (Box 0220, Folder 5)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Eduction Improvement Project (Reports and Pulblications) 1966 (Box 0220, Folder 6)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Eduction Improvement Project (Correspondence) 1964-66 (Box 0220, Folder 7)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Education Improvement Project (Reports and Publications) 1964-65 (Box 0220, Folder 8)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (Nashville Education Improvement Project) 1970-71 (Box 0220, Folder 9)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Nashville Education Improvement Project 1969 (Box 0220, Folder 10)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Nashville Education Improvement Project 1968 (Box 0220, Folder 11)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Nashville Education Improvement Project 1967 (Box 0220, Folder 12)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Nashville Education Improvement Project 1966 (Box 0221, Folder 1)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Nashville Education Improvement Project 1965 (Box 0221, Folder 2)
- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools--Nashville Education Improvement Project 1964 (Box 0221, Folder 3)
- Southern Association of Science and Industry 1945-50 (Box 0221, Folder 4)
- Southern College and University Union (SCUU) 1974-75 (Box 0221, Folder 5)
- Southern College and University Union (SCUU) 1973 (Box 0221, Folder 6)
- Southern College University Union 1970-72 (Box 0221, Folder 7)
- Southern College University Union 1969 (Box 0221, Folder 8)
- Southern Education Reporting Service 1969 (Box 0221, Folder 9)
- Southern Education Reporting Service: Saturday, 4-27-68 9am SERS board Meeting, Statler Hilton, airport (Box 0221, Folder 10)
- Southern Education Reporting Service: SERS Board Meeting, 4-2-67 (Box 0221, Folder 11)
- Southern Education Reporting Service: Mr. Heard (Box 0221, Folder 12)
- Southern Education Reporting Service: Southern Education Reporting Service 3/25-26/66 (Box 0221, Folder 13)
- Southern Education Reporting Service: SERS (Meeting of Executive Committee of Board of Directors) 7-24-65 (Box 0221, Folder 14)
- Southern Education Reporting Service (See transfer file) 7/65-68 (Box 0221, Folder 15)
- Southern Education Reporting Service (See transfer file) 8/64-6/65 (Box 0221, Folder 16)
- Southern Education Reporting Service: SERS committee meeting, Atlanta, July 13-14, 1964 (data) (Box 0221, Folder 17)
- Southern Education Reporting Service April 1, 1964-7/64 (Box 0221, Folder 18)
- Southern Education Reporting Service Feb. 1, 1963-3/64 (Box 0222, Folder 1)
- Southern Education Reporting Service--Correspondence (See transfer file) 1954-62 (Box 0222, Folder 2)
- Southern Education and Reporting Service--By-Laws and Minutes, etc. 1954-59 (Box 0222, Folder 3)
- Southern Methodist University 9/5-11/62 (Box 0222, Folder 4)
- Southern Newspaper Publishers Association Foundation (Reed Sarratt, Executive Dir.) 1970-74 (Box 0222, Folder 5)
- Southern Political Science Association 1970-75 (Box 0222, Folder 6)
- Southern Political Science Association 1967-69 (Box 0222, Folder 7)
- Southern Political Science Association (Box 0222, Folder 8)
- Southern Political Science Association--Travel Folder (Chancellor Heard) Oct. 31-Nov. 2, 1963 (Box 0222, Folder 9)
- Southern Regional Council 1971-73 (Box 0222, Folder 10)
- Southern Regional Council 1970-71 (Box 0222, Folder 11)
- Southern Regional Council 1963-69 (Box 0222, Folder 12)
- Southern Regional Education Board 1973-74 (Box 0222, Folder 13)
- Southern Regional Education Board 1972 (Box 0222, Folder 14)
- Southern Regional Education Board 1971 (Box 0222, Folder 15)
- Southern Regional Education Board 1970- (Box 0222, Folder 16)
- Southern Regional Education Board 1969 (Box 0222, Folder 17)
- Southern Regional Education Board 1952-59 (Box 0222, Folder 18)
- Southern Regional Education Board Questionnaire Copy 2 1956 (Box 0222, Folder 19)
- Southern Regional Education Board (Master's degree in Nursing) 1952-54 (Box 0222, Folder 20)
- Southern Regional Education Board 1957-68 (Box 0222, Folder 21)
- Southern Research Institute 1948-59 (Box 0222, Folder 22)
- Southern Rural Life Council 1942-46 (Box 0222, Folder 23)
- Southern University Conference 1978-79: Southern University Conference 4/19-21/79 (Box 0223, Folder 1)
- Southern University Conference 1978-79: Southern University Conference 1978 (Box 0223, Folder 2)
- Souhtern University Conference 1978-79: Southern University Conference 4/6-8/78 (Box 0223, Folder 3)
- Southern University Conference 1978-79: Southern University Conference--Agenda and General Information 4-78 (Box 0223, Folder 4)
- Southern Univesity Conference 1978-79 (Box 0223, Folder 5)